# VISHNUPARTTHI PALANISAMY

75/35 Harrington Road, Shenoy Nagar Chennai, Tamilnadu, India

| Tel: +919894602049 | vishnu121.gasc@gmail.com

#### PERSONAL DETAILS

D.O.B: 2nd Sep, 1989 | Gender: Male | Nationality: Indian | language: Tamil (Native), English (Business Fluent),

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

A review of my CV will quickly confirm to you that I have worked with various companies where I utilized my skills and expanded my knowledge and gain wide experience. In each and every task I was undertaking, I was able to complete it in the given time deadline and I assure you that I can successfully fulfill any obligations requiring of any responsibility upon your company.

#### KEY SKILLS AND COMPETENCIES

- Customer Service
- Problem-solving
- Communication
- Mentoring
- Prospecting the New Leads

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

Business Administrator Vishnu Hydraulics | June 2017- Present

## Duties and Responsibilities

- Interviews and Hiring Staffs, Planning and organizing
- Negotiation and Decision Making
- Leadership and Communication
- Superior Interpersonal to Handle Customer Service
- Training new employees and Mentoring

#### Sales Manager

ICICI Bank Ltd | Apr 2013 - Sep 2016

### Duties and Responsibilities

- Providing Client Service to Existing Customers
- Prospecting and Identifying New Leads
- Strategizing & Implementing ways to Achieve Sales Targets

#### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

 $\bullet$  "CHENNAI SOUTH SANGAMAM" for outstanding performance in CASA NCA for the period of H1-FY 2013-2014

#### EDUCATION BACKGROUND

#### B.Sc Physics (Computer Applications)

Gobi Arts & Science College, Affiliated by Bharathiyar University, Coimbatore, Tamilnadu | Mar 2007 - Mar 2010

### Master of Computer Applications (MCA)

K. S. Rangasamy College of Technology, Anna University, Chennai, Tamilnadu | Apr 2010 - Mar 2013

#### Post Graduate in Diploma Computer Applications

Adithya Info Tech | Mar 2008 - Sep 2008

#### HOBBIES

- Reading
- Playing Chess and Puzzle Games
- Travelling
- Cooking